{"items": [{"question": "extremely large", "answer": "Astronomical", "options": ["astrologer", "astronaut", "Astronomical", "cosmonaut"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "who interprets the influence of the heavenly bodies on human affairs.", "answer": "astrologer", "options": ["astronaut", "astrologer", "nautical", "cosmonaut"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "trained for spaceflight.", "answer": "astronaut", "options": ["aster", "nautical", "astronaut", "cosmonaut"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "a Russian, trained for spaceflight.", "answer": "cosmonaut", "options": ["asterisk", "nautical", "cosmonaut", "aster"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "of or pertaining to sailors", "answer": "nautical", "options": ["asterisk", "nautical", "aster", "astrophysics"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "any composite plant of the genus having rays varying from white or pink to blue around a yellow disk.", "answer": "aster", "options": ["aster", "astrophysics", "asterisk", "disaster"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "a small starlike symbol (*)", "answer": "asterisk", "options": ["asterisk", "disaster", "astrophysics", "autonomy"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "branch of astronomy that deals with the physical properties of celestial bodies", "answer": "astrophysics", "options": ["autonomy", "astrophysics", "metronome", "disaster"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "An state of extreme misfortune", "answer": "disaster", "options": ["metronome", "disaster", "autonomy", "geometry"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "independence or freedom", "answer": "autonomy", "options": ["autonomy", "metronome", "geometry", "geography"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Clicking pendulum indicates the exact tempo of a piece of music", "answer": "metronome", "options": ["metronome", "biopsy", "geography", "geometry"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "the branch of mathematics that deals with points", "answer": "geometry", "options": ["geometry", "geography", "autopsy", "biopsy"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Study of the earth's surface includes people's responses to topography and climate and soil and vegetation", "answer": "geography", "options": ["biopsy", "zodiac", "geography", "autopsy"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "the removal for diagnostic study of a piece of tissue from a living body.", "answer": "biopsy", "options": ["zodiac", "biopsy", "autopsy", "entomology"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "inspection and dissection of a body after death postmortem examination.", "answer": "autopsy", "options": ["zodiac", "entomology", "autopsy", "insect"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "a circular diagram representing the 12 zodiacal constellations and showing their signs", "answer": "zodiac", "options": ["insect", "entomology", "zodiac", "tonsillectomy"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "the branch of zoology dealing with insects.", "answer": "entomology", "options": ["entomology", "insect", "appendectomy", "tonsillectomy"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Small air-breathing arthropod", "answer": "insect", "options": ["tonsillectomy", "Astronomical", "appendectomy", "insect"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "the operation of excising or removing one or both tonsils.", "answer": "tonsillectomy", "options": ["Astronomical", "tonsillectomy", "appendectomy", "astrologer"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "excision of the vermiform appendix", "answer": "appendectomy", "options": ["Astronomical", "astrologer", "appendectomy", "astronaut"], "answer_index": 3}], "title": "Session 12.txt", "total": 20}